[{"question":"","answer":""},{"question":"According to the article, Taiwan has the best healthcare system in the world.","answer":"false"},{"question":"According to the article, Taiwan has one of the worst healthcare systems in the world.","answer":"false"},{"question":"The article states that people often _____ the amount of time they spend on social media.","answer":"underestimate"},{"question":"The article mentions pull all-nighters. Which of the following is closest in meaning to this phrase?","answer":"stay up all night to finish tasks"},{"question":"Which of the following is NOT mentioned in the article as a benefit of getting regular exercise?","answer":"clearing your skin"},{"question":"According to the article, what are the advantages of better time management?","answer":"We can eat better, sleep better and boost our overall health."},{"question":"Which of the following sentences best describes the main idea of the article?","answer":"We can take better care of each other by learning to take better care of ourselves."},{"question":"Based on the article, more than forty percent of the world’s countries have _____ for every one thousand people.","answer":"fewer than one doctor\nmore than ten doctors"},{"question":"The article states that people often underestimate the amount of time they spend on ____.","answer":"social media"},{"question":"The article states that students who slept less than six hours per night for two weeks felt _____ students who didn’t sleep at all for 48 hours.","answer":"as bad as"},{"question":"Based on the article, more than _____ of countries in the world have fewer than one doctor for every 1000 people.","answer":"forty percent\nfour percent"},{"question":"Based on the article, working on smaller, easier tasks first is a good way to avoid ______ on your","answer":"schoolwork"},{"question":"The article mentions sleep on it. Which of the following is closest in meaning to this phrase?","answer":"don’t try to do everything at once"},{"question":"The article provides information on which three areas?","answer":"exercise, time management and sleep"},{"question":"According to the article, eighteen million _____ workers will be needed to reach the UN’s 2030 goal.","answer":"healthcare"}]